Guide to the Language Resource Center collection, circa 1963-1983.
Language Resource Center collection,
- Reel-to-reel tape recordings
  - LCTL published
    - Korean, Undated; TR-13371; FSI (Box 28)
      LRC #: K 8
    - Korean, Undated; TR-13372; FSI (Box 28)
      LRC #: K 9
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13373 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 41
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13374 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 42
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13375 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 43
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13376 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 44
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13377 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 45
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13378 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 46
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13379 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 47
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13380 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 48
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13381 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 49
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13382 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 50
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13383 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 51
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13384 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 52
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13385 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 53
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13386 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 54
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13387 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 55
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13388 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 56
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13389 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 57
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13390 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 58
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13391 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 59
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13392 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 60
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13393 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 61
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13394 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 62
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13395 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 63
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13396 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 64
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13397 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 65
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13398 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 66
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13399 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 67
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13400 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 68
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13401 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 69
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13402 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 70
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13403 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 71
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13404 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 72
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13405 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 73
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13406 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 74
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13407 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 75
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13408 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 76
    - Comedies - Taipei, Undated; TR-13409 (Box 32)
      LRC #: TAI 77
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13410; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 1.1
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13411; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 1.2
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13412; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 1.3
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13413; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 10.1
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13414; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 10.2
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13415; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 10.3
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13416; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 11.1
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13417; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 11.2
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13418; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 11.3
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13419; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 12.1
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13420; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 12.2
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13421; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 12.3
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13422; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 12.4
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13423; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 13.1
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13424; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 2.1
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13425; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 2.2
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13426; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 2.3
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13427; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 3.1
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13428; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 3.2
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13429; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 3.3
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13430; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 3.4
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13431; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 4.1
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13432; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 4.2
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13433; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 4.3
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13434; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 5.1
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13435; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 5.2
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13436; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 5.3
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13437; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 5.4
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13438; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 6.1
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13439; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 6.2
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13440; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 6.3
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13441; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 7.1
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13442; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 7.2
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13443; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 7.3
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13444; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 7.4
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13445; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 8.1
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13446; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 8.2
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13447; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 8.3
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13448; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 9.1
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13449; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 9.2
    - Hungarian, Undated; TR-13450; FSI (Box 33)
      LRC #: HG 9.3
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13451; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 1
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13452; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 10
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13453; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 11
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13454; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 12
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13455; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 13
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13456; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 14
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13457; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 15
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13458; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 16
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13459; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 17
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13460; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 18
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13461; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 19
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13462; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 2
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13463; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 20
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13464; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 21
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13465; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 22
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13466; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 23
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13467; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 24
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13468; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 25
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13469; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 26
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13470; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 27
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13471; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 28
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13472; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 29
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13473; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 3
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13474; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 30
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13475; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 31
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13476; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 32
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13477; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 33
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13478; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 34
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13479; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 35
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13480; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 36
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13481; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 37
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13482; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 38
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13483; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 39
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13484; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 4
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13485; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 40
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13486; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 41
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13487; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 42
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13488; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 43
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13489; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 44
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13490; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 5
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13491; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 6
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13492; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 7
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13493; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 8
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13494; FSI (Box 40)
      LRC #: MG 9
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13495; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 203
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13496; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 204
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13497; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 205
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13498; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 206
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13499; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 207
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13500; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 208
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13501; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 209
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13502; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 163
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13503; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 164
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13504; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 165
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13505; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 166
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13506; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 167
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13507; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 168
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13508; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 169
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13509; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 170
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13510; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 171
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13511; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 172
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13512; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 173
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13513; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 174
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13514; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 175
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13515; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 176
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13516; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 177
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13517; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 178
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13518; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 179
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13519; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 180
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13520; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 181
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13521; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 182
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13522; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 183
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13523; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 184
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13524; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 185
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13525; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 186
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13526; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 187
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13527; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 188
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13528; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 189
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13529; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 190
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13530; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 191
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13531; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 192
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13532; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 193
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13533; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 194
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13534; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 195
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13535; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 196
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13536; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 197
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13537; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 198
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13538; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 199
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13539; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 200
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13540; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 201
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13541; FSI (Box 41)
      LRC #: MG 202
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13542; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 210
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13543; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 211
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13544; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 212
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13545; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 213
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13546; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 214
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13547; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 215
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13548; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 216
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13549; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 217
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13550; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 218
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13551; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 219
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13552; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 220
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13553; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 221
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13554; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 222
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13555; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 223
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13556; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 224
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13557; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 225
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13558; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 226
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13559; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 227
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13560; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 228
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13561; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 229
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13562; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 230
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13563; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 231
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13564; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 232
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13565; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 233
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13566; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 234
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13567; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 235
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13568; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 236
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13569; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 237
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13570; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 238
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13571; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 239
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13572; FSI (Box 44)
      LRC #: MG 240
    - Classical Arabic “A Course in Levantine Arabic”, Undated; TR-13573; University of Michigan; Found in “Bad Box” (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARL 15
    - Classical Arabic “A Course in Levantine Arabic”, Undated; TR-13574; University of Michigan; Found in “Bad Box” (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARL 16
    - Classical Arabic “A Course in Levantine Arabic”, Undated; TR-13575; University of Michigan; Found in “Bad Box” (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARL 17
    - Classical Arabic “A Course in Levantine Arabic”, Undated; TR-13576; University of Michigan; Found in “Bad Box” (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARL 18
    - Classical Arabic “A Course in Levantine Arabic”, Undated; TR-13577; University of Michigan; Found in “Bad Box” (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARL 4
    - An Introduction to Egyptian Arabic, Undated; TR-13578; Found in “Bad Box” (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARE 1
    - An Introduction to Egyptian Arabic, Undated; TR-13579; Found in “Bad Box” (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARE 10
    - An Introduction to Egyptian Arabic, Undated; TR-13580; Found in “Bad Box” (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARE 11
    - An Introduction to Egyptian Arabic, Undated; TR-13581; Found in “Bad Box” (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARE 12
    - An Introduction to Egyptian Arabic, Undated; TR-13582; Found in “Bad Box” (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARE 13
    - An Introduction to Egyptian Arabic, Undated; TR-13583; Found in “Bad Box” (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARE 14
    - An Introduction to Egyptian Arabic, Undated; TR-13584; Found in “Bad Box” (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARE 15
    - An Introduction to Egyptian Arabic, Undated; TR-13585; Found in “Bad Box” (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARE 16
    - An Introduction to Egyptian Arabic, Undated; TR-13586; Found in “Bad Box” (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARE 17
    - An Introduction to Egyptian Arabic, Undated; TR-13587; Found in “Bad Box” (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARE 18
    - An Introduction to Egyptian Arabic, Undated; TR-13588; Found in “Bad Box” (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARE 19
    - An Introduction to Egyptian Arabic, Undated; TR-13589; Found in “Bad Box” (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARE 2
    - An Introduction to Egyptian Arabic, Undated; TR-13590; Found in “Bad Box” (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARE 20
    - An Introduction to Egyptian Arabic, Undated; TR-13591; Found in “Bad Box” (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARE 3
    - An Introduction to Egyptian Arabic, Undated; TR-13592; Found in “Bad Box” (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARE 4
    - An Introduction to Egyptian Arabic, Undated; TR-13593; Found in “Bad Box” (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARE 5
    - An Introduction to Egyptian Arabic, Undated; TR-13594; Found in “Bad Box” (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARE 6
    - An Introduction to Egyptian Arabic, Undated; TR-13595; Found in “Bad Box” (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARE 7
    - An Introduction to Egyptian Arabic, Undated; TR-13596; Found in “Bad Box” (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARE 8
    - An Introduction to Egyptian Arabic, Undated; TR-13597; Found in “Bad Box” (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARE 9
    - Intro to Modern Arabic, Undated; TR-13598; Found in “Bad Box” (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARZ 1
    - Intro to Modern Arabic, Undated; TR-13599 (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARZ 2
    - Intro to Modern Arabic, Undated; TR-13600 (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARZ 3
    - Intro to Modern Arabic, Undated; TR-13601 (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARZ 4
    - Intro to Modern Arabic, Undated; TR-13602 (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARZ 5
    - Intro to Modern Arabic, Undated; TR-13603 (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARZ 6
    - Intro to Modern Arabic, Undated; TR-13604 (Box 50)
      LRC #: ARZ 7
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13605; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 45
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13606; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 46
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13607; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 47
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13608; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 48
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13609; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 49
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13610; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 50
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13611; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 51
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13612; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 52
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13613; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 53
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13614; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 54
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13615; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 55
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13616; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 56
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13617; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 57
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13618; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 58
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13619; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 59
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13620; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 60
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13621; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 61
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13622; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 62
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13623; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 63
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13624; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 64
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13625; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 65
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13626; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 66
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13627; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 67
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13628; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 68
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13629; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 69
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13630; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 70
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13631; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 71
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13632; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 72
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13633; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 73
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13634; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 74
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13635; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 75
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13636; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 76
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13637; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 77
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13638; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 78
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13639; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 79
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13640; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 80
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13641; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 81
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13642; FSI (Box 52)
      LRC #: MG 82
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13643; FSI (Box 53)
      LRC #: MG 123
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13644; FSI (Box 53)
      LRC #: MG 124
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13645; FSI (Box 53)
      LRC #: MG 125
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13646; FSI (Box 53)
      LRC #: MG 126
    - A Modular Approach to Mandarin, Undated; TR-13647; FSI (Box 53)
      LRC #: MG 127